you are a repressed little sister who is
eres una marija reprimida que estás
in the closet and does not want to come out and
dentro del armario y no quieres salir y
until they stick a good bazooka in your
hasta que no te metan un buen bazoka en
[ __ ] and dilate it well you are not going to be
el ojete y te lo dilaten bien no vas a
happy so have a happy
ser feliz así que que pases feliz
birthday with that hemorrhoid face and that
cumpleaños con esa cara almorrana y ese
swollen object that was found at a
inflamado que se ha encontrado en una
gas station gref I can't believe it and
gasolinera gref no me lo puedo creer y
gref has not wished him Look look look look sucking up to him
gref no le ha desiado Mira mira mira
Luisa How
mira haciéndole la pelota Luisa Qué
false Luisa says one thing is the
falsa Luisa dice una cosa es el
character and another the person and I fall in love
personaje y otra la persona y me enamora
So from now on it is another of my
Así que a partir de ahora es otro de mis
children my protégé How false How false and
niños mi protegido Qué falsa Qué falsa y
looking for fame I mean in two weeks he says that
busca fama o sea en dos semanas dice que
what gref did was the character I didn't do it
lo de gref era el personaje no lo hice
I did my character but let's see
yo lo hizo mi personaje pero vamos a ver
lady if they are reporting him a
señora si lo están denunciando un tema
judicial matter it is not a character as I am
judicial no es un personaje como estoy
seeing comments in addition to children that I
viendo comentarios además de niños que
love with my soul comments about
amo con mi alma comentarios sobre lo de
the photographs of gre's kid
las fotografías de del chiquillo de gre
that I have
que yo de no tengo
absolutely nothing of ass licker what I have done
absolutamente nada lo que lo he hecho